Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - FETF: Academic Freedom, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - FETF: Controller's Report, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Duplicates of Letters, Memoranda, etc. sent daily, 1969-1972 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Material, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Evaluation of Chairman, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Doctoral Dissertations Relating to NYC, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Leadership Game - Student Pack # 1, undated (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Certification, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Fact Sheet of Operations, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Dean Lou Kleinman Weekly Report, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 250 7
  - Dean Lou Kleinman Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Dean John Payne Weekly Report, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Dean John Payne Faculty Resignation Acknowledgement, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Dean John Payne Sabbaticals - Approval or Denial, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Dean John Payne Confirmation of Faculty Appointments, undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Dean John Payne Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Professor J. Richards - Acting Dean - Weekly Report, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Professor J. Richards - Acting Dean (A. Spinner) Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Professor Aileen Schoeppe - retired, undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Professor Frank Silverblank - Acting Dean - Weekly Report, undated (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Professor Frank Silverblank Acting Dean - Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Dean Stasia Ziobrowski - Weekly Report, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Dean Stasia Ziobrowski - Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Commencement, 1971-1973 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Calendars, 1969-1973 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - UCEA Board of Trustees Meeting, 1961-1964 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - UCEA Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - UCEA Board of Trustees, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - UCEA Resource Materials for Usin in Simulated School Workshops, undated (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - UCEA: Symposium Papers - Leadership in 1970s, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 251 5
  - UCEA: Instructional Materials, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - UCEA: Culbertson Correspondence, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - UCEA: Development of a Plan for Advancing Educational Administration, 1969-1974 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - UCEA: Culbertson Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - UCEA: Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - UCEA: Instructional Materials, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - UCEA: Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - UCEA: Publications - Case Series in Educational Administration, undated (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - UCEA: Newsletter, 1958-1966 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Ed Admin. Quarterly, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - "Introducing UCEA", undated (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Culbertson: Common and Specialized Content in the Preparation of Admin., undated (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Culbertson: Preparation of Educational Administrators, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Culbertson: Development of Concepts Basic to Design of Modern Programs, undated (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Culbertson: Money Needed and Where it Will Come From, undated (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Culbertson: Program for Recruiting Ed. Leaders of Unusual Promise, undated (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Culbertson: The Preparation of Administrators, undated (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Perception: Griffiths, Ramey and Iannacone, undated (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Harlow: Purpose - defining: Central Function of School Administrator, undated (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Hencley: Functional Interrelationships Among Various Admin. Positions, undated (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Immegart: The Unadorned Building, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 252 3
  - OHM - Leadership Game, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Lortie: Complexity, Specialization and Professional Knowledge, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Mailing List, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Millet: Perspectives on Public Administration, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Policy Statement "Training for Use", undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Preparation Program in Ed Administration - Purdue University, undated (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Reller: The Preparation of Administrators: New Perspectives, undated (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Schutz: Creative Behavior: Evaluation of a Training Method, undated (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Taped Best Lecture Series, undated (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - UCEA Committee: Improving Preparatory Programs for Ed. Administration, undated (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Walton: The Education of Educational Administrators, undated (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Willis: Training Administrators - New Perspectives, undated (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - UCEA Set # 1 Materials, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - UCEA Miscellaneous Materials, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - UCEA Seminar: Career Development, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - UCEA Seminar: Education and Rade Relations, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - UCEA Seminar: The Professorship in Educational Administration, undated (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - UCEA Seminar: Professional Development, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - UCEA Seminar: AT&T Leadership Training, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - UCEA Seminar: Sixth Year Career Development, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - UCEA Seminar: Mental Health and School Administration, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - UCEA Seminar: Research, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - UCEA Seminar: Teachers College, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - UCEA Seminar: Stencils - 5th Career Dev., 1960 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - University of Chicago, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Northwestern University, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Harvard University, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - University of Illinois, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Research Seminar, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Research Conference, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - In-Baskets & DCS, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 253 1
  - In-Baskets & DCS, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 254 9
  - AASA Conventions, 1964-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 255 6
  - AERA Preparing Research Personnel for Education, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - AERA Convention and other Material, 1962-1967 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Messages - Possible in-basket material, 1962-1967 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence A - S, 1980-1983 (Box 88)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 256 4
  - General Correspondence T - Z, 1980-1983 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 257 2
  - Annual Reports, 1964-1968 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 258 0
  - Annual Report to the President on School of Education, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 259 8
  - Annual Report of School of Education, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Department Annual Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - School of Education, Financial Report, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Public Recreation and the Negro: Study, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Wyandanch Suffolk County, New York, U.F.S.D. # 9: Community Analysis, undated (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Feasibility Study, undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Progress Report, Research Program in Early Childhood Education, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Fourth Annual Report the W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Baltimore Vocational Study, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - A Study of the Feasibility of Creating a Secondary School within NYU, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Handbook on Recruitment of Potential Industrial Arts Teachers, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Final Report of the Experienced Teacher Fellowship Program in English, 1966-1967 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - School of Education, Financial Report, 1968-1969 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript of Book, "Politics of Public Education" by Laurence Iannaccone, undated (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - A Study of School Plant and Program Requirements, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Manhasset Report, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Final Report, Faculty and Other Professional Staff in Higher Education, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Fifteen Year Educational Projection: Ramapo Central School District, 1967-1982 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 260 6
  - Study of the US Office of Education, 89th Congress, Second Session, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Harlem Institute for Teachers, 6th Cycle Proposal, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Computer Assisted Instruction Project, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Attitudes and Perceptions of Desirable Traits and Behaviors of Teachers, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Report: Brain-Damaged Children, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Progress Report: Eastern Regional Institute for Education, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Report to Center for Urban Education: Study of the Compensation Program, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Testing Linguistically-Oriented Materials for Teaching of Writing in NYC, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Educational Technology Report, undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Student Life at Washington Square, undated (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Griffiths, Daniel E.:The Job Performance of School Administrators, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Report of Census on Personnel Matters Affecting 1969-1970 Budget (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, Loeb Student Center, 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Pilot Study of Art Facilities at Six Colleges and Universities, E.M. Benson, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Cost of a Schoolhouse: Report from Educational Facilities Laboratories, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Yearbook 1968: Teacher Education: Issues and Innovations (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Partnership in Teacher Education, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - AACTE Publications, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 261 4
  - Cremin: "The Education of the Public", undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - AASA, Annual Report of the Executive Secretary, 1966-1967 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - The Federal Government and Public Schools, AASA, undated (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Basic Program Plans, Center for Urban Education, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - A Climate for Individuality, AASA, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Strengthening State Associations of School Administrators, AASA, undated (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, Southern Illinois University, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, New York State School Boards Assoc., undated (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - The Campaign for Yale, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Problems of Financing Education for All School Children, H. Thomas James, undated (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Phi Lamda Theta, Education Book List, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - The Problem of Poverty - What Can Be Done? NYPGA Bulletin, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - A Survey Report on Public Information Programs in the St. Depts. Of Ed., 1968 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Dimensions of Executive Positions, John K. Hemphill, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Hartsdale Board of Education Review, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Services to Eudcation Publications, undated (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - NYC Board of Examiners, Examiniation for License as School Pschologist, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - National Foundation for Educational Research in England and Wales, undated (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Program for Situational Analyses, Barbara McNeill, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Cooperative Program in Educational Administration, Mid-Atlantic Region, 1952 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - School Population Projection for Levittown, NJ, 1956 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Improving the Education and Preparation of NYC Students for Careers.., undated (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Three Year Report of the Public Education Assoc.'s Youth and Work Project, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Report on the 1963 Seminar for the Study of Advanced Administration (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Studies in the Dynamics of Administrative Interaction: UC Berkeley, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - What the Forecasters Say of the Future, Bottomly, undated (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Cues to Effective Teaching and Teacher Education, Doll and MacDonald, undated (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Who Shall Train the Administrators of Our Schools?, undated (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Nebraska Community Education Project, Hayes and Bonneau, undated (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Teacher Behaviors Related to Classroom Efficiency and Effectiveness, undated (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - A Study of the Whitman School Faculty, Robert Josephson, undated (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Organizational Problems of Educational Research, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Main Currents in Modern Thought, undated (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Public Policy Studies: Approach to Governmental Research, Ostrom, undated (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Creative Problem-Solving, University of Buffalo, undated (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - UNC Two-Year Program in School Administration, undated (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - Role Expectations and Perceptions of School Principals, undated (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Educational Administration in Oklahoma, undated (Box 93, Folder 39)
  - Theories of Choice in Business, undated (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - Tables for Comparing Related-Sample Percentages and for the Median Test, undated (Box 93, Folder 41)
  - Toward the Education of Administrators: Uses of the Social Sciences, undated (Box 93, Folder 42)
  - System Development Corporation Publications, undated (Box 93, Folder 43)
  - The Oregon Program, A Design for the Improvement of Education, 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 44)
  - "How Can School Boards Secure More Adequate Support of Public Ed.?", 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 45)
  - A Manual for School Administrators, Anderson, Baldwin, Beauchamp, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 46)
  - Annual Report of the Cooperative Center for Educational Adminstration, 1955-1958 (Box 93, Folder 47)
  - Role of the Teacher in the Classroom, Amidon and Flanders, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 48)
  - Research Report: Brother Joseph D'Agostino, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 49)
  - Technical Report of the Director of the National Defense Education Act, 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 50)
  - Dean Anderson general correspondence, bibliography and speeches, undated (Box 93, Folder 52)
  - Report: Workshop for Administrative Personnel in Large School Communities, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 262 2
  - Faculty Seminar on Educational Theory Proceedings, 1960-1961 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Your AASA in 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Special Memorandum to AASA Members, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Trends in Financing Public Education, National Education Association, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Stateside: Focus on Format, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Report on Administrative Staffing for Westchester Joint School District, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, Loeb Student Center, 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Foundations in Educational Administration, Dr. Maurice J. Thomas, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Criteria of Performance in School Adminstration, Ohio Educational Assoc., undated (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Paradigm for Research, undated (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Community Organization Book, Request for Permission to Quote, undated (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - National Survey of Curriculum Articulation Between College and Sec. Schools, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Influences on American Education, Harvard Graduate School of Education, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - High Priority Areas in School Personnel Administration, Harold E. Moore, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Final Report, The Oregon Program, 1962-1967 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Students, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Bridges to Slum-Ghetto Children: Studies in Learning to Become a Teacher, 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Foundation: "Role of the College and University Trustee", 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - City of Toronto Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Conference on Urban Education, Yeshiva, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Study of Administration in Westchester School District, 1957 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Study of Administration in the Willioughby School District, undated (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Present and Proposed Organization & Administration of Westchester Schools, 1957 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - DCS - Statistical Analysis, undated (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - National Conference to Improve the Effectiveness of State Supervision of Music, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Technical Report of the Direcotr of the National Defense Education Act, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - "Developing Taxonomies of Organizational Behavior in Education", 1964 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports: School of Ed, Administration & Supervision, GSAS, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Dean Anderson's Annual Report, undated (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 263 0
  - State of the School, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Deans' Comments - State of the School, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Social Work, 1967-1968 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Statement for Hester, Academic Goals and Financial Needs, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - The "Method of Inference" in Foreign Language Study, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - A Demonstration of the Use of Simulation in the Training of School Admin., 1967 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Seminar on Elementary and Secondary School Education in Visual Arts, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Research Report:Teacher Supply and Demand in Public Schools, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Research Project: Role Expectations and Perceptions of Principals, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - The Puerto Rican Study, Board of Education, NYC, 1953-1957 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Report to the Faculty of School of Education, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Rating Forms, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Admissions and Registration, undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - New Education Building, undated (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Report of the Committee to Study the Doctoral Program, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Project APEX, undated (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Minutes of the Senate Meeting, undated (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - President Hester's Report to the NYU Senate, undated (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Position Description (Vice Dean), undated (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Study of Puerto Rico, undated (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Virgin Islands First Annual Report, undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Reactions - Mission of the School, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - First Half of Annual Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Second Half of Annual Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 350 5
  - Plans for the Decade Ahead, 1964-1973 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - The Van Pit Series - Thinking, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Dean Anderson's Correspondence to Faculty, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Peace Corps, undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Conant: Conference on Books, undated (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Conant: Comments / Deans Report, undated (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Requests for Conant Report, undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Conant: Reviews and Releases, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - "Our Changing Schools of Education", Francis S. Chase, undated (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - "Goals and Plans of Departments", undated (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - The Role of the School of Education, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 351 3
  - Problems and Potentials of Library Service - The Role of the Faculty, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - NJ State of Education Dept., undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - All-Square Student Congress, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Correspondence, Chancellor Russell D. Niles, undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Dean Arnold Goren: Monthly Reports on Admissions, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Program 613, Human Development and Social Relations, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Robert E. Martin, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - National Conference to Improve the Effectiveness of State Supervision of Music, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Industrial Arts Department, undated (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Purpose of School of Ed, Kerlinger, undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Brian Holmes, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Seminar on University and College Administration, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Hugh Banks, undated (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Louis J. Hoffman, undated (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Beverly Lipschitz, undated (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Division of Social and Philosophical Foundations of Education, undated (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - S.M. (Mike) Miller, undated (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Jeanne L. Noble, Office of Education Case, undated (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Dr. P.C. Sexton, Research, undated (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Richard Schultz, undated (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Learning of Scientific Conceptual Systems and Methods of Investigation, undated (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Thirty-nine Theses and Counter-Theses on Psychoanalysis, undated (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Proposed Certificate Program in School Psychological Services, undated (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Edna Levine, Research, undated (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Tri-University, National Invitiational Conference on Elementary Education, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 266 3
  - Upward Bound, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Comm. On the Sch. Of Ed., undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - University Scholars, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Cost Study, undated (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Teacher Corps, Look Mag. Article, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Harold Taylor, Meting in Schiffer Room, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Virgin Islands, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Virgin Islands Graduation, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - CASEA, Eugene Oregon, undated (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - New York State Education Department, undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - List of Stencils, undated (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Street Academy Program, undated (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Student Strike, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Sterling Forest, undated (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Social Indicators Seminar, Sub-Committee on Government Research, undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Summer Session, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Radio Liberty, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Redefer: Cooperative Study of Educational Personnel, undated (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Post-Session, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Final Figures, 1970-1971 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Research Training Program, 1968-1969 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Requests for Publications of Faculty Writings, etc., undated (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Remodeling, undated (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Sterling Forest, Planning Conference, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Board of Education, 1968-1969 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Shriver: Commencement Address, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Seminar on the Theories of Administration, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Secretarial Services, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - S.A.L.T., 1968 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Student Teaching, 1963-1968 (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - Swedish Workshop, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - Symposium for Hagerstown Board of Education, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - Special Faculty Meeting, Francis S. Chases' Remarks, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - Malverne Report, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 36)
  - Teacher Corps, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 267 1
  - Commission on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Transparencies re New Building, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rican Study, 1953-1957 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Study of Puerto Rico, undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Virgin Islands First Annual Report, undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Virgin Islands, undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Redefer: Proposed Educational Personnel and Develop. Center in Sch. Of Ed., undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Financial Data, 1965-1966 (Box 99, Folder 9)